missmustardseed.com 2018-10-29

# Disclosure - Miss Mustard Seed

This policy is valid from 24 November 2010

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. For questions about this blog, please contact [marian@missmustardseed.com](mailto:marian@missmustardseed.com).

By reading this blog, you acknowledge that you are doing so of your own free will and you are taking and following the information provided at your own risk.

Unless otherwise noted, I am the legal copyright holder of the material and pictures posted on my blog. My material may be used by peer blogs, if it is linked to my blog and I am given credit for my pictures and ideas. My images may also be pinned on Pinterest or shared through FaceBook, Twitter and other forms of social media if they are linked to my blog and I am given credit.  My content may not be published, copied, or reprinted without my consent.

The information I provide on my blog is based on my own experience and is my own opinion. You are reading and following my advice at your own risk. Please always use safety precautions when performing a DIY project and always read and follow manufacturer’s directions for the products and tools you use.

I respect the privacy of my readers and will never sell your contact information to another company or put you on a spam list. I am not responsible for the privacy practices of my advertisers or blog commenters.

I reserve the right to change the focus of my blog, shut it down, sell it or change the terms of use at my discretion at any time.

I am not responsible for the actions of my advertisers, sponsors or blog commenters. If you purchase a product through a link from my blog, you must take action with that company to resolve any issues, not this blog.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner of this blog receives compensation for my posts or advertisements, I always give my honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

And here’s some more yada-yada privacy policy stuff, but you may be interested…

Privacy Policy for http://www.mms2.wpengine.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at missmustardseed@gmail.com.

At http://www.mms2.wpengine.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.mms2.wpengine.com and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, http://www.mms2.wpengine.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

http://www.mms2.wpengine.com does not use cookies.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.mms2.wpengine.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.mms2.wpengine.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.mms2.wpengine.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
http://www.mms2.wpengine.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.mms2.wpengine.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
